{
    "subject": "resource/The_Legend_of_White_Fang",
    "predicate": "ontology/network",
    "object": "resource/HBO",
    "human_readable": "The Legend of White Fang is part of HBO's network.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.93594890832901,
            "question": "Is The Legend of White Fang part of HBO's programming?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8264761567115784,
            "question": "Are there other shows like The Legend of White Fang on HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8102472424507141,
            "question": "What television network is home to The Legend of White Fang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8045087456703186,
            "question": "How popular is The Legend of White Fang on HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7270629405975342,
            "question": "Which streaming service might feature The Legend of White Fang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7196900248527527,
            "question": "What type of program is The Legend of White Fang likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6304222941398621,
            "question": "Who might have produced The Legend of White Fang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5401840806007385,
            "question": "What genre does The Legend of White Fang likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4595136344432831,
            "question": "What is the general plot of The Legend of White Fang likely to be about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3678359091281891,
            "question": "Has The Legend of White Fang won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Legend of White Fang is part of HBO's network.",
            "html": "dbpedia_301_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the general plot of The Legend of White Fang likely to be about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_301_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does The Legend of White Fang likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_301_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have produced The Legend of White Fang?",
            "html": "dbpedia_301_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_164.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_301_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"The Legend of White Fang\" was broadcast on HBO, which supports the statement that it is part of HBO's network."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}